Do you believe in gravity
between individuals?
Do you believe that fate brought
us together for a reason?
Why in God's name? Why?
Why did it have to end like this? Why?
Why can't I just die and be with Perla?
My fury isn't satisfied.
I'll make you pay right here and now.
Whether I'm going to eliminate you?
And those without any memories
left are as good as dead.
I can't
believe it,
but I can't believe it.
Thank you so
much for watching.
You dumbass!
Don't you know how to drive properly?
You better not be driving
like this on purpose!
Yeah, right, like I have the
composure to mess around!
Just look!
These bugs are eating me alive, too!
Weather...
huh?
I sense Poochie in that direction.
And Weather is there, too.
Are they together?
I can't say that with all certainty,
but I know they're near each other.
Weather...
What the actual hell did you just say?
You want me to kill you?
I do. Cut the bullshit!
What do you mean by that?
What's going on with you?
I remember this happening
around me once before.
In my hometown in 1988. Say what?
It would seem this freak show
represents the darkest side of my heart.
Your memories, they really are back.
So you remember everything now?
Then get your act together
and do something about this!
I have no control over this ability.
though if you kill me the Stan's power
should stop I do kind of feel bad
for the snail people but a part of me
hates living even more and that part is
enjoying the hell out of this somewhere
down in the deepest recesses of my
heart I feel some relief to be honest I'm
sort of glad this happened what are you
but Jolene if she's nearby
could she be turning
into a snail too you
better not Move carelessly.
I have no idea how all this works,
but judging by what I can see,
it's likely that touching these snails
is the trigger to this phenomenon.
Moreover, if you turn snail,
there'll be no one left to kill me.
What kind of fucking nonsense is
coming out of your mouth, you bastard!
I don't want to hear it!
Tell me where Jolene is right now!
Yeah, fine, but only after we
settle things with Poochie.
I told you, that so-called
priest is somewhere nearby.
what really where he's here at this
point my only hope for staying alive
is to settle things between us once
and for all from what happened to
ff to sealing away jolene's father's
memories for his own selfish desires
to come to fruition i'll settle it
all i'll be the one to kill poochie
and once he's taken care
of you kill me got it fine
whatever i still owe ff a
big one anyways i'm with you
speaking of which where's
the priest is he north or
south it isn't about where
he's coming from the man's
already here and he's
somewhere within 20 meters of
us i've already done a quick
sweep for him underground
using my diver drive all
i can see are these snails
Are you positive he's closing
in on us through all this?
Weather forecast!
There's no disturbance
in the air currents.
And I don't sense anything in the
area breathing or moving around.
What if he's hiding
inside that car, Weather?
Weather!
I am already well aware of how that
weather-controlling ability of yours functions.
This phenomenon that turns
anything man or beast into snails.
As long as I understand the
secret behind why it happens,
I have absolutely no reason to be
afraid of the snails touching my body!
I've uncovered how this works,
although it took me a while to figure out
the specific intricacies of your ability.
I have overcome it once
before when I removed
your memories in 1988 son of a damn you!
It's all over for you now, too?
You should have stayed out of my
business and away from Jolene.
But instead of patiently
waiting for your prison
sentence to end you chose
to end your own life!
I don't get it.
How is Poochie standing there unscathed?
These snails don't make any sense.
What's going on here, Weather?
With this, let's call it good.
If you're planning to die sometime
soon, Weather, hold off for a while.
I cut your leg off so it would take
a few hours for you to bleed out.
With this deadly phenomenon
you cause still in play,
it'll be the perfect weapon for putting an
end to all nuisances who
attempt to oppose me.
I now know who will be raising
me up to attain heaven.
Whether it turns out to
be you, not anyone else.
We still have three days until the new moon
arrives, and then it will finally begin.
The moment that the green baby
desired will come to pass,
and the manifestation of
heaven that Dio strived for?
will take root inside of my body.
With Diver Drive, I gave Weather a leg
by phasing into his body.
Weather forecast!
Grab the priest and bring
him closer, Weather!
Your big brother's stand
isn't a power type like yours!
If you can keep a hold of him, you
can outmatch him at point-blank range!
Grab him!
And don't you dare let him get away!
White?!
Weather!
Damn it!
What just happened?
I wasn't even anywhere
near touching the snails.
Poochie!
What sort of game are you playing?
What the hell did you do?
Subliminal messaging.
The method of cleverly
arranging hidden words on
a poster that cannot be
noticed at first glance.
Or a single frame containing an image that
has been clipped into the film of a movie.
The average person is unaware
of ever having seen the image.
But without a doubt,
it becomes carved into their deep
consciousness and lingers there.
And that's what psychologists
refer to as subliminal
messaging and the effect
it has on the subconscious.
Things or images that are
instinctive penetrate much further
into one's consciousness more than
if they are witnessed directly.
And as a result of this, they control
what an individual may decide to do.
And now the rainbow's weather forecast
conjured are having that same effect.
It's becoming a subliminal
message at an atmospheric level.
And whenever they lay their eyes on them,
it's entering the souls
of the townspeople.
Is it because images of snails
are being projected onto them?
Or could it be because it
stimulates primitive instincts?
Everyone who looks at the rainbow starts
to think that they too will become snails.
And these intense thoughts affect
the subjects physically as well.
What the hell?
What are you trying to explain here?
This is the true answer.
The truth behind the ability
weather forecast had sealed away.
In the past,
when the same phenomenon occurred to
the innocent people in my hometown,
I saw that a blind old woman was
completely unaffected and that's when
I understood the solution to getting
rid of this strange occurrence.
Being blind you can't
weather even if I can't see
I can still sense where
you are with my intuition.
And this will work long after I've
removed my ability to use my eyes.
But let me tell you closing your
eyes now will not save you Anastasia!
There is no way to escape
from the subliminal
messaging once it has dug
its roots into your soul.
As long as weather
continues to draw breath,
this destructive
phenomenon will never end.
I think I'll take your other leg as well.
You will not stand ever
again! Dive or try!
Don't you dare lash out at me
with your insignificant feelings!
Humans must strive to
reach the gates of heaven!
and the one who is the
first to find and attain
it will be able to lead
all of mankind to it.
You two are merely
interfering with my progress!
All because I have to sacrifice the lives?
of a few people to do so.
Diamon Quo Fats!
To be crucified!
Now die for your sins!
What the?
What is this?
What's happening?
this is your doing isn't it weather what
are you up to now what is this atrocious
scraping sound what on earth do you think
you're doing something that i can control
one of weather forecasts abilities
it doesn't have to be fast
but if i make it precise and if
i keep it simple he's evaporating
his blood freezing it in the air
and hardening it weather's He's
using all the blood on the ground
to surround him with spears,
and the priest can't even see it!
So what are you gonna choose?
You have the option to continue
this without the use of your vision.
And the other option
that you have to choose
from is seeing what's going
on with your own eyes.
But if you trip and
fall, it's over for you.
Here I come, Pucci.
Get ready.
You're done, Poochie.
There's no way you're
going to escape from this.
Are you going to bring your eyesight back?
Go ahead and try.
I'll just reflect the rainbow
straight into your face.
If weather can grab you, your
chances of survival are slim to none.
In terms of power, Pale
Snake is simply outclassed.
Weather's got this in the bag.
Hmm.
I anticipated that you
would try to do something.
There is not a reality where you
would ever let me go peacefully.
You who has finally
regained his lost memories.
However!
Anastasia!
There are eyes for me to
see out of from all over.
That's how I was able to come here.
Anastasia, may I use you for a moment?
You shall act as a substitute for my eyes.
Would you kindly relate to me
what you see in front of you?
Specifically the things
that are dangerous to me.
What is Weather doing currently?
He's hardening his own
blood to create a few
dozen spears all over
the ground around you.
There are three of them
placed directly behind you.
Then to your right there
are four more lying in wait.
Ah, I see.
Now be a good boy and guide me out
of this maze of blood spears, okay?
Please continue.
If you take three steps,
you'll meet six spears.
From there, you're gonna
want to take a hard left.
Weather.
From the very moment you were
born, a curse has afflicted you.
Stay there silently, just as you are.
No matter what you attempt to do,
there is no salvation for your life.
The memories I sealed away should never
have been returned to
you in the first place.
Continue going left for
five steps, then face right.
After that, you're free from any danger.
Splendid.
Five more steps.
Correct. Just five.
This is something I just realized,
but I saw it, so I'll tell you.
One more spear still remains.
I was only looking at the ground,
so I didn't notice before.
There's some blood on your shoulder,
and right about now, weather's
hardening it into another spear.
Oops.
It's too late.
Eww, playing these dirty tricks!
Like hell any of this is dirty!
Weather's just stronger than you!
And that's why he's gonna win!
This wind pressure's soaked!
I must get as far away as I can from
the range of his stand immediately!
I have to dodge this one blow!
If I can dodge it, then Weather's
stamina should reach its limits!
Get impaled by your own blood spears!
It's useless to resist.
That attack's nothing to Weather.
He can dodge it easily!
Yes, I have no doubt that he will.
But then the direction of his
wind pressure will change.
That's my chance to flee!
I've got you.
I've finally got you now.
He didn't dodge them.
Weather actually took the spears
and use them to capture the priests!
He's within Weather's range!
Did he get him?
Don't do it, Weather.
While you were in Green
Dolphin Street Prison,
I could have finished you off at any
given moment if I truly wanted to except I
had it in my head that one day I could save
you which is why I stole your memories.
This isn't some convenient excuses
if I'm begging for my life.
Prime numbers.
Listen to me brother.
I did all the wrong with you.
Three.
I've worked tirelessly towards my goal of
attaining the power so that
both of us can prosper.
There must be someone who obtains
the power to reach heaven.
It was It's faded to happen eventually!
Seven.
Stop it, Weather.
Eleven.
Thirteen.
This is not an end to both of our lives!
Seventeen.
This is just sad.
The kind of evil that doesn't
even realize it's evil.
It's the most disgusting kind of them all!
Nineteen.
Pooch is afraid.
His expression.
There's fear and despair written
all over his face! Twenty-three. No.
Stop this weather!
You are the one who's wrong!
You're the cursed one, brother!
I'm the man who kept you alive,
and this is how you remain!
It's over!
Die, Keicho!
What the hell are you doing?!
I thought I told you that if you
tried anything weird, I'd kill you!
No, wait!
There was a sudden cloud
of dust and then a stray
nail or something stabbed
straight through the tire!
It isn't my fault I lost control!
Shut up, he's close.
Weather is somewhere nearby.
The priest, too.
Although, something looks off outside.
You're right.
I can't see very well, but there's
something strange covering up the road.
Weather!
I know you're close by!
Respond to me! Weather!
What is going on out here?
What kind of crazy horror scene is this?
I can sense the priest
moving around nearby.
He's super close.
I need to find Weather
fast before it's too late.
I have a feeling that something
terrible is happening.
Is this wind being stirred
up by Weather's ability?
Has that damn priest not
turned into a snail yet?
I honestly have no idea.
I only know that he's here!
Let's find him!
Jolene!
I just saw someone!
He's over there!
I don't know if it's weather or the
priest, but they're in that direction.
Jolene, the wind's starting to disperse.
Also, my body's turning back to normal.
Does this mean...
OUCHI!
Hold on, Jolene!
Our bodies and stands
still haven't recovered
all the way from
transitioning into snails.
We can't beat the priest now
in terms of power and speed.
We have to find weather first.
Well, if we beat the priest,
we can find weather, too!
Stone Ocean!
Join!
What the? Weather!
Nobody is capable of
catching up to me anymore.
I suggest you enjoy the
rest of the days you
have left with your family and loved ones.
Coming after me now is utterly useless.
I always win.
Don't do it, Jolene!
Anastasia!
This man is no longer the priest.
Who we know as Father Poochie
isn't here anymore. What?
This is a revelation.
That's not him either.
It's one of his abilities.
He made an afterimage.
Versus!
Using the cover of the wind,
the priest planted a past
memory to this poor guy's head.
He used his own ability to
craft an image of himself.
The presence you were
feeling earlier was Versus.
Pucci took this chance to execute him.
This is a revelation.
It would seem there's something on my
side that can only be classified as fate.
The threads of fate are
aiding me in reaching
heaven in three days during the new moon.
If it were not for destiny, I
would have surely been defeated.
You believe in gravity.
That is the reason why every
one of you came here today.
Weather!
I told you, it's not him.
No one can pursue me! Can pursue me!
Can pursue me!
The snails are all gone.
This is...
Where's Weather, Anastasia?
Where did he go?
Hermes, did you see him?
Can you not feel his presence anymore?
You mean you really
can't tell where he is?
Emporio!
Hey, Yermis. He's there.
Call a doctor.
He should have healed
from the snails by now.
Emporio!
Jolene!
I'm sorry.
The wind stopped.
The rainbow disappeared too, Jolene.
No way.
It can't be.
Is this because we crashed the car?
Or is it because I came after him?
But why?
Listen, Jolene.
Plenty of people have
called me a murderer.
At least that's what the newspapers said
about me, and I don't necessarily disagree.
When people asked me if I would sacrifice
myself for my family, I told them all no.
I don't think my answer
would change even now.
When it came to my parents, my
heart was never moved by them.
However,
I know I'd be willing to
risk my life for those that
revived me from the dead
without a second thought.
It was like that for Weather, too.
That's...
Yeah.
When Pale Snake was focused
on dealing the final blow,
he took advantage of his special ability.
He used that moment to seal
his ability into a disc.
Hey, Jolene.
I think Weather entrusted this to you.
Weather came back to life when he
finally escaped from that prison.
And that's the proof he left for you.
In his final few days, he was happy.
Weather had already been saved.
Mother.
One more time.
I want to speak with you.
Just one more time.
Just once more.
I want to talk to you in the soft breeze.
Thank you.